(卢蒙)
早上好 斯科特先生
Good morning, Mr. Scout.
1 2 3 4 5
One, two, three, four, five,
6 7 8 9 10 11 12
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12.
32 33 34
Thirty-two, 33, 34,
35 36 37...
35, 36, thirty-se--
人生切割术
第二季 第三集
(失踪)
好 赫莉和我会去寻找 山羊男和其他潜在的山羊员工
Okay, me and Helly will find the goat man and other possible goat people.
迪伦 你去新的休息室
Dylan, hit the new break room.
也许有些其他部门也会用那里
Maybe some of the other departments use it too.
好 之后吧
Yeah. Maybe later.
好的 这事儿挺要紧的 迪伦
Okay. This is kind of important, Dylan.
是 我工作状态正佳 但别担心 我会去办的
Yeah. I'm in a good groove here, but don't worry about it. I'll get to it.
好 把画像给他们看 记得带上
Okay. Well, just show them the sketch. Do not leave it behind.
光学与设计部
O&D.
没错 欧文 你能行的
Yes, Irv. You can do this.
我知道
I know.
你们真觉得他们会任由我们到处晃
You guys really think they're gonna let us roam around?
视频中说了我们想去哪儿都可以
They said on the video we can go wherever we want.
卢蒙在聆听员工呢 记得吗
Lumon is listening, remember?
我以为意思是他们在监听我们的对话
I thought that meant they were listening to our conversations.
他说得对 马克 我的确 感觉到那句话有两层含义
Yeah, he's right, Mark. I did get the hint of a double meaning.
我们会低调点的
Well, be discreet.
如果他们对我们的举动不知情 要怎么惩罚我们
If they don't know we're doing it, how can they punish us?
嘿 你没回过那边吧
Hey, you haven't been back there, have you?
没有
No, no.
我们会支持你的
We've got you.
谢谢你 赫莉
Thank you, Helly.
假设我们找到了她...
So, say we find her...
什么
Sorry?
假设我们到了山羊部 他们说
Say we get to the goat department and they're like,
“是的 凯西女士在这里 她在这个山羊笼子里”
"Yes, Ms. Casey's here. She's in this goat cage."
到时候我们怎么办
What do we do then?
我们将她带到南边的楼梯间 我会和她一起去...
Well, we get her to the south stairwell... I'll go with her...
走出门后 我外面的自己 会知道该怎么做的
and once we're out the door, my outie'll know what to do.
是 好的 看来你都计划好了
Right. Okay. Well, sounds like you've got it figured out.
你确定你这么帮我没问题吗
Are you sure you're okay helping me out with this?
当然
Yeah, of course.
那就好
Okay, good.
是
Yeah.
我...
I... I...
迪伦
Dylan.
我以为你要去光学与设计部
I thought you were going to O&D.
迪伦
Dylan.
我重新创作了这些画
I've recreated the paintings.
我和你提到的那些画 我外面的自己创作的画
The ones I told you about. The ones my outie was working on.
什么
What?
我一直在想
You see, I've been thinking.
也许那条走廊其实在这里
Maybe the hallway is really down here.
也许我梦到的就是那个
Maybe that's what my dreams have been.
我们可以去找找看 迪伦
We could look for it, Dylan.
我们今天就可以去找
We could go today.
你可以陪我一起
You could accompany me.
是
Yeah.
是 我会想想的
Yeah, maybe.
或者你可以自己找  这样更容易隐藏踪迹 对吧
Or maybe you go yourself, like, for stealth, you know?
- 隐藏踪迹  - 对
- Stealth? - Yeah.
听着 我很难解释 就是...
Look, I can't really explain. I just--
黄小姐
Miss Huang.
通行证
Hall pass.
一切可好
Everything chill?
迪伦G 请跟我来
Dylan G., come with me, please.
早上好 塞斯
Good morning, Seth.
娜塔莉
Natalie.
你的气球有点儿垂头丧气啊
Looks like your balloons could use some coffee.
- 之前摆在了... - 我连上了董事会
- They were in the-- - I've got the Board.
是
Of course.
你好
Hello.
董事会说“你好”
The Board says, "Hello."
你好 我想先为最近的晋升 向董事会致以谢意
Hello. I want to thank the Board humbly for my recent betterment.
董事会说“不客气”
The Board says, "You're welcome."
董事会对于你的升职感到喜悦
The Board is jubilant at your ascendance.
希望你感觉受到重视 并询问你是否有此感受
It wants you to feel appreciated and asks if you do.
我有的
I do.
董事会非常郑重地表达 其希望你感到卢蒙的历史与你息息相关
The Board austerely desires for you to feel connected to Lumon's history.
就此
To that end,
请接受董事会赠予你的 这些经重新规范化的画作
please accept from the Board these inclusively re-canonicalized paintings
借此帮助你在本公司创始人 基尔身上找到共鸣
intended to help you see yourself in Kier, our founder.
噢 天啊
Oh, my.
画了整个基尔周期呢
You'll find the whole Kier cycle.
董事会也想表达 本人 即娜塔莉
The Board wishes to express that I, Natalie,
在接受我目前的职位之时 也收到了同样的赠礼
received the same gift upon receipt of my current position
并为此感到深切的感动
and found it extremely moving.
我很感激
I'm grateful.
是
Yes.
这很有意义 看到自己纳入了...
It's meaningful to see myself reflected in...
董事会已终止通话
The Board has concluded the call.
恭喜 塞斯
Congratulations, Seth.
(盐颈 383公里)
就是这里吗
Is that it?
应该是的
Think so.
你要...
You're gonna--
你确定
You sure?
好
Okay.
好的 来吧
All right. Okay, we're doing this.
你能看到什么吗
Can you see anything?
不能 小心 有大便
No. Careful, there's poop.
好
Okay.
好的
天啊
Oh, my God.
搞什么
What the hell?
你们是来杀我的吗
Are you here to kill me?
不是的...我...抱歉 你好 我是马克
No, no, no, no, no, no. I... Sorry. Hi, I'm Mark.
- 我是赫莉 - 我们是宏观数据精检部的
- I'm Helly. - And we're with Macrodata Refinement.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
哺乳动物培育部
Mammalians Nurturable.
我们没有恶意 只是想聊聊
Please, we mean you no harm. We just wanna talk.
拜托了
Please.
(光学与设计部)
欧文
Irving.
费莉西亚 你好
Felicia, hello.
我很抱歉过了这么久之后突然来访
I'm sorry to pop in after all this time.
你一定很忙
I'm sure you must be very busy.
见到你很开心
It's good to see you.
她叫凯西女士
Her name's Ms. Casey.
她是我们的健康部前任主管
She's our former Wellness Director.
健康部...
Wellness...
本部不允许这种无用小事的存在
we don't abide such fripperies here.
是 她已经退任了 但我们认为也许她还在这一层
Right. Well, she's been retired, but we believe she may still be on the floor.
你确定不认识她吗
Are you sure you don't know her?
也许你们应该拿上这张纸离开
Maybe you should take that page of paper and be on your way.
你先回答我的问题
Not until you've answered my question.
马克
Mark.
(卢蒙)
叫你们走的时候就该走
You should have left.
我挺想知道现在是要去做什么
It would be cool to know what this is about.
还有 一直问为什么你是个小孩 会很无礼吗
So, like, is it rude to keep asking why you're a kid?
我无意冒犯 但就想确定 你是安全的吧
I don't mean to impugn. It's just like, are you okay, you know?
他们不是逼迫你来这上班的吧
They're not, like, forcing you to be here, are they?
噢 糟糕
Oh, fuck.
我们为什么来保安室
Why are we going to the security room?
我的天
Wow.
迪伦
Dylan?
嗨
Hi.
迪伦G 鉴于你的良好行为和工作成绩
Dylan G., through good behavior and output,
你获得了奖励 可与你外面自己的妻子见面18分钟
you've earned an 18-minute visitation event with your outie's wife,
她叫格雷琴G
Gretchen G.
酷啊
Cool.
现在开始计时
Your time begins now.
我们坐下吧
Should we sit?
包很好看
Nice sack.
你说什么
Sorry?
你的...
Your... The--
谢谢 他们让我把个人物品放在这里
Thanks. They made me put my stuff in here.
厉害
Badass.
你真的完全不知道我是谁
You really don't know me at all?
是的 我是说 刚才看到的照片里有你 但...
No. Well, I mean, from the photos from just now, but...
对 塞斯提醒过我 说这样见面可能会有点奇怪
Yeah, Seth warned me that this might be weird.
- 塞斯是谁  - 你不...
- Who's Seth? - Don't you--
请避免分享可能机密或敏感的信息
Please refrain from sharing information that may be privileged or sensitive.
多谢
Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
那个小孩是谁啊
Who is that child?
黄小姐
Miss Huang.
听着 很高兴认识你 但我是惹祸了吗
Look. It's really nice to meet you, but am I in trouble?
噢 没有 你没有惹祸
Oh, no. No, you're not in trouble.
我们有三个孩子
We have three kids.
是
Right.
而你...
And you...
不 是他 或是...
No, he... Or--
我丈夫做其他工作时总是做不长
My husband has had trouble keeping other jobs.
他很蠢吗
He dumb?
不是
No.
人很混账
He a dick?
不是
No.
那他有什么毛病
What is wrong with him?
他没毛病
Nothing's wrong with him.
他只是...
He just...
他一直都没找到自己擅长的工作
He never quite found his thing.
所以他其实是个废材
So he's actually kind of a fuck up?
你想不想看看孩子的照片
Do you wanna see a picture of the kids?
好啊
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
吉姆六岁 他现在上一年级
So, Jim is six. He's in the first grade now.
露丝四岁
And Ruth is four.
梅瑞克刚满两岁
And Merrick just turned two.
天啊
Wow.
我的妈呀
Holy shit.
看看他们
Look at them.
好棒
They're awesome.
是的
They are.
我们住在牧场
And we live on a cattle ranch?
然后...伯特说
And then... And Burt says,
“就算你是拜德伊根我也不在乎
"I don't care if you're Baird goddamn Eagan,
别来我的部门 教我怎么打印雪花玻璃球”
you don't come to my department and tell me how to print a snow globe."
我真...天啊 他天不怕地不怕
I ca... My God, he was fearless.
我和伯特共事了六年
I worked with Burt for six years.
我只见过他怕一件事
And I only ever saw him scared of one thing.
他第一次去找你之前 花了两个小时弄自己的头发
He spent two hours on his hair the first time he went to visit you.
真的
Really?
我应该给你看个东西
I should show you something.
- 如果看到她... - 不是她 是...
- If we see her-- - Not her. It's a...
这个
Here.
噢 欧文 画得真好
Oh, Irving, it's lovely.
只要是没见到他的一天 我就会画一张
I'd draw one every day I couldn't see him.
我的业绩下滑了 但我都不在乎
My numbers went down, but I didn't even care.
噢 不 这不是伯特
Oh, no. That's not Burt.
这画的不是他 那只是...随便画画的
That's something else. That's just a... That's nothing.
这是...
It's...
你怎么知道出口走廊的
How do you know about the exports hall?
什么
I'm sorry?
我们很多的货都是从那儿寄出的
We send a lot of shipments there.
以前我们会自己去寄
Used to go ourselves.
但现在他们派了一个专人来取货
But now, they send a guy.
你记得它在哪儿吗
Do you remember where it is?
你们好
Hello.
嗨
Hi.
- 不好意思 你见过这个女人吗  - 嘿 给我停下
- Excuse me. Have you seen this woman? - Hey! Stop that!
她叫凯西女士 她曾是健康部主管
Her name's Ms. Casey. She was the Wellness director.
- 停下 - 你们有谁见过她吗
- Stop that! - Have any of you seen her?
够了 我们已决定派一位信使 去通知米尔奇克先生你们来过这里
Enough! We've decided to send a courier to inform Mr. Milchick of your inquiry.
不 你不能这么做 如果被他们发现 他们可能会杀了她
No. You can't do that. They could kill her if they find out--
这和哺乳动物部无关
That's not a Mammalians problem.
这是公司里的自己的问题
It's an innie problem.
听着 我们过去也惧怕其他部门...
Listen, we used to be afraid of other departments too--
我们才不怕你们
We're not afraid of you.
听着 他们让她“被消失”了
Look, they just disappeared her.
如果我们允许这种事发生在凯西女士身上
And if we let this happen to Ms. Casey,
那发生在我们自己身上时 谁还能为我们挺身而出呢
then who's gonna step up when it happens to us?
如果你们的某只山羊失踪了 你们不会去找它吗
If one of your goats went missing, wouldn't you go looking for it?
她以前会来我们的饲养箱里 进行她的治疗谈话
She used to come do her sessions in our husbandry tanks.
她很温柔
She had a gentle way about her.
她说我外面的自己拥有高超的观星技术
She said my outie excels at stargazing.
那话对我意义重大
Meant a great deal to me.
就我们所知 她退休了 如他们所说的
As far as we know, she was retired, just like they say.
但如果你怀疑另有隐情 我们不会阻碍你们的调查
But if you suspect otherwise, we won't hinder your search.
谢谢你
Thank you.
是的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
但在你们走前 我们要...
But before you go, we would...
看看你们的肚子
like to see your bellies.
我们的肚子
Our bellies?
拜托了
Please.
好吧
Okay.
瞧 没有囊袋
See? Pouchless.
这证明不了什么
Proves nothing.
好吧 我们...
Okay. Let's--
- 我们就...对 - 是
- So we'll just... Yeah. - Yeah.
我很高兴我们见面了
I'm glad we did this.
我希望这样能帮你...不知道呢
I mean, I hope, for you, this was... I don't know.
是 有帮到
Yeah, it was.
我会好好的 我会让你们都感到骄傲的
And I'll be good. I'm gonna make you all proud.
我一直为你感到骄傲 迪伦
I'm always proud of you, Dylan.
酷
Cool.
我爱你
I love you.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 说惯了 - 不 这...
- Habit. - No, it's...
好吧
Okay.
好的
All right.
- 拜拜 - 是
- Bye. - Yeah.
别忘了梅瑞克耳朵那件事 好吗
So remember Merrick's ear thing, okay?
知道
Copy that.
- 是左耳 - 好
- Left ear. - Yep.
你给吉姆的课准备好曲奇了吗
And did you do the cookies for Jim's class?
拜拜
Bye.
这周轮到我们做曲奇
It's our week for cookies.
我没做曲奇 抱歉
I did not do the cookies. Sorry.
是一个柱体 你只需要切成一片片
So, it's a tube and you just need to slice them
- 然后放进烤箱 - 懂了
- and then you put them in the oven. - Got it, yeah.
爱你
Love you.
嘿 见得怎么样
Hey, how was the thing?
见什么
What thing?
见我
The thing with me.
挺好的
Yeah, it was good.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
怪怪的好 但挺好的
Weird good, but good.
酷
Cool.
对 好了...明早见
Yeah. Okay. Okay, okay. I'll see you in the morning.
- 拜拜 - 拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
“但啤酒和薄荷茱莉普 显然无法填补爱留下的空洞
"But surely beer and juleps cannot fill the void left by love.
事实上 只有葡萄酒能填补 但葡萄酒是出了名的昂贵
Indeed, only wine can achieve this, but it is famously costly,
因此悲伤是穷人最常见的问题之一”
which is why sadness is among the most recurrent issues facing the poor."
写得真好 观察敏锐
Remarkable. So astute.
是吗 这正是我的目标
Is it? That's what I was going for.
嗨
Hi.
宝贝
My babe.
这是卢蒙的娜塔莉凯伦
This is Natalie Kalen from Lumon.
出了什么事吗
Is everything okay?
没有 完全没有
Yes. God, yes.
其实 娜塔莉只是过来讨论我的书的
Natalie just stopped by to discuss my book, actually.
见到你真开心 德文 你一定感到很自豪
It's a joy to meet you, Devon. You must be so proud.
是的
I am.
你一定已经知道了 你丈夫的作品
I'm sure you know by now that your husband's work
出现在我们公司的分离楼层了
has found its way onto our severed floor.
是的 查出怎么出现在那里没有
Yeah. Do we know how that happened yet?
其实我们已经讲完那件事了 现在正在讨论的是...
So we've actually moved beyond that, and we are now discussing the--
你用的那个词是什么来着
What was the term you used?
- 结果 - 结果
- The result. - The result.
里肯的文字对我们的员工 产生了深远的影响
Ricken's words have had a profound effect upon our workers.
我们认为他看到了事物的关键
We think he's really tapped into something.
娜塔莉想讨论 出版一个《你的身份》的版本
And Natalie wants to discuss a version of The You You Are,
专门针对公司里的自己
specifically for innies.
好吧 挺好的 但是 现在的版本有什么问题吗
Okay, well, that's cool. I mean, but what's wrong with the current version?
没有问题
Nothing.
不 其实解释的原因挺有趣
No, the explanation is actually very interesting.
事实上 非常引人深思 还是你来说吧
It's fascinating, actually. You, please.
公司里的自己更偏好某一种措辞方式
There's a certain verbiage to which innies respond more favorably.
所以能调整一下用词会更好
If we just tweak it here and there.
他们认为这样能带来很大的改善
They think that it could be a real game changer.
懂了
Gotcha.
我得走了 但她一小时后要喝奶 所以...
I gotta go. But she needs a bottle in an hour. So...
没问题
Of course.
- 德文 - 怎么
- Devon. - Yes?
我只想说 你哥哥是 我们分离层员工中最善良的其中一位
Can I just say, your brother is one of the sweetest members of our severed team.
对 他是个好人
Yeah, he's a good egg.
好的 一小时啊
Okay. One hour.
她说她叫娜塔莉
So she said her name's Natalie?
好像是娜塔莉凯伦
Natalie Kalen, I think.
(多功能粘性胶水)
她...是来问什么 问我最近做什么还是...
What... Was she asking, like, what I'm up to or--
不 因为他们找的是里肯
Nope, 'cause it's Ricken they're after.
- 里肯  - 对 他的书
- Ricken? - Yep. His book.
什么
What?
似乎那本书极大地启发了你和你的同事
I guess you and your work friends were so inspired by it.
- 噢 老天爷 - 对
- Oh, Jesus Christ. - Yep.
所以他们...想出版一个 针对公司里的自己的特版
That they're... They wanna do like an innie specific cut.
天 好吧 真是... 我有很多话 但我还是不说了
Wow, okay. Well, there's just... There's a lot I'm not gonna say.
感谢你的不说之恩
And that is so appreciated.
你把我们在这做的事告诉里肯了吗
Have you told Ricken what we're doing here?
- 你疯了 当然没有 - 好的
- Are you insane? No. - Okay.
那就好
Good.
所以你需要看事后两分半钟的图像
Okay, so you need to see the afterimage for, like, two and a half minutes?
2分18秒
Two minutes, 18 seconds.
大概是从停车位到电梯
It's from the parking spot to the elevator, give or take.
(活着的是谁 )
是 健康大脑协会一定会为你感到自豪
Yeah, I think the Whole Mind Collective would be very proud of this.
你的幼儿园老师也是
As well as your kindergarten teacher.
她叫什么名字来着 拉斯特嘉顿老师
What the fuck was her name? Mrs. Lustgarten?
- 对 拉斯特嘉顿老师 是 - 天
- Yeah, Mrs. Lustgarten. Yeah. - Wow.
她很懂我
She really got me.
好的 该死 我得走了
Yeah. Fuck, I gotta skedaddle.
你小心点 好吗
Will you be careful, please?
好
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我爱你
I do love you.
好的
Okay.
虽然在皮普烧烤店你让我买单 混蛋
Even thought you left me with the check at Pips, you dick.
谢了
Thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
(管理控制台 人员:4)
(进行中的监视名单)
2 3 4 5
Two, three, four, five,
6 7
six, seven,
8 9 10
eight, nine, ten,
11 12 该死
11, 12. Shit.
该死
Fuck.
想要我回去 你们必须满足我的需求
If you want me back, you must accommodate my needs.
请说
I'm listening.
宏观数据精检 没有讨论余地
MDR. Non-negotiable.
马克S只差一点就完成冷港了
Mark S. is so close to completing Cold Harbor.
我想完成自己发起的项目
I intend to finish the work that I started,
所以
which is why
米尔奇克必须走
Milchick must go.
他不具备处理这一职责的能力
He's not equipped for the task.
必须由我担任分离层经理
I must be floor manager.
我听出了自大
I hear ego...
狂妄
hubris...
傲慢
arrogance.
基尔教导我们 这些只会造成痛苦
Kier teaches us they only cause pain.
我的一切成绩都是通过...
Everything I accomplished, I earned...
自己的勤恳耕耘所取得的
through dedication and industry,
不是因为我含着金汤勺出生
not because I was born into it.
我认为你高估了自己的贡献
I think you've overestimated your contributions
低估了自己的幸运
and underestimated your blessings.
我们不是非要请你回来不可
We didn't have to ask you back.
你们没有选择
You didn't have a choice.
你确定
Are you sure?
不如我们重新来过吧
Why don't we reset?
不是非要用这样的方式
It doesn't have to be this way.
娜塔莉
Natalie.
请问问董事会是否有空
Please see if the Board is available
与科贝尔女士和我通话
for Ms. Cobel and myself.
我们一起去和他们谈谈吧
Let's go speak with them together.
哈蒙妮
Harmony.
33 34 35 36
Thirty-three, 34, 35, 36,
37...
thirty s--
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你是想将讯息刻在视网膜上 给公司里的自己传信吗
Are you trying to burn a message to your innie into your retinas
因为电脑说这是个高明的办法
because your computer told you that was a brilliant idea?
对
Yeah.
不...什么 不行...
No, no. What? No, no, no, no, no.
你在...什么
What are you... What?
这样没用
It doesn't work.
- 也不奇怪 - 那个开关只会短暂散瞳
- No shit. - The switch briefly dilates the pupils.
只是重启
Clean slate.
- 好了 谢谢你 谢了 - 而且你可能会把自己弄瞎
- Okay, thank you. Thanks. - Also, you could blind yourself.
你公司里的自己又要如何回话
And how was the innie gonna send you a message back?
那是他的问题 我不知道
That's his problem. I don't know.
马克 开门
Mark, unlock the door.
为什么
Why?
我们得聊聊
We need to talk.
- 天啊... - 马克 开门...
- Oh, my God. - Mark, unlock the--
马克 把该死的车门打开
Mark, unlock this fucking door!
要命 这破玩意
Goddamn it. This goddamn fucking thing.
- 什么  - 有个更简单的方式
- What? - There's an easier way.
对皮蒂来说好像不怎么简单
Didn't seem particularly easy for Petey.
听说了紧急加班事故
Heard about the OTC.
对 我妹妹和我公司里的自己 说过话 他说了很多事情
Yeah, my sister talked to my innie. He said a lot of things.
他有没有告诉她 你妻子在卢蒙 还活着
Did he tell her your wife is alive at Lumon?
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
她活着吗
Is she?
珍玛还活着吗
Is Gemma alive?
对 我上次见到她时是的
She was, the last time I saw her.
你为什么不告诉我
How could you not tell me?
如果你没忘 我们当时被人打断了
We were interrupted, if you recall.
马克 我想帮你 但你必须信任我
Mark, I want to help you, but you have to trust me.
要怎...
How the fu...
有一种办法 唯一的办法 能将讯息传入和传出卢蒙
There is one way, and one way only, to get information in and out of Lumon,
那就是恢复记忆
and that's reintegration.
我的技术已经改善了 我可以帮你恢复得更好
I'm better at it now. I can make it work with you.
我可以将那个爱她的版本 与另一个版本的你缝合...
I can sew together a version of you that loves her with a version of you that can--
好 你做吧
Yes. Do it.
你确定吗
You're sure?
我想见我的妻子
I wanna see my wife.
(千伏和毫安 指针颤动表示过载)
监控器区分公司内外自己的
The monitors differentiate the five brain wave frequencies
五种脑波频率
of the innie and outie.
德尔塔 太塔 阿尔法 贝塔 伽马
Delta, theta, alpha, beta, gamma.
每个示波器一个频率 两种脑波
One frequency, two waves per oscilloscope.
脑波没有同步 至少现在没有
The waves aren't in sync. Not yet, anyway.
这就是我们的目标
That's what we're here to do.
前倾
Lean forward.
会疼吗
Is it gonna hurt?
理想的话不会
Ideally not.
你嘴里有什么味道
What does your mouth taste like?
没有味道
Nothing.
很好
Good.
搞什么
What the fuck?
糟糕
Shit.
你还好吗
You all right?
不知道 你说呢
I don't know. Am I?
我先问简单的问题 然后越来越复杂
I'm gonna start with easy questions and get more complex.
你记得规程吗
Do you remember protocol?
- 这是第一个问题  - 不 还没开始
- Is that the first question? - No, we haven't started yet.
是 我记得
Yes, I remember.
身体放松 结束时 你应该感觉很好的 我是谁
Relax your body. You should feel good when this is over. Who am I?
好的 那...
Okay, so are--
我们开始了 我是谁
We've started. Who am I?
艾萨尔瑞伽比
Asal Reghabi.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
我的地下室
My basement.
你母亲叫什么
What was your mother's name?
芬恩斯科特
Fern Scout.
她的眼睛是什么颜色
What was her eye color?
不是吧
Seriously?
棕色 是棕色的
Brown. It was brown.
你爱她吗
Did you love her?
爱
Yeah.
说一个水坝的名字
Name a dam.
胡佛水坝
Hoover.
MDR是什么意思
What does MDR stand for?
什么
What?
MDR
MDR.
- 神秘... - 错了
- Mystic-- - That's wrong.
说一个让你感到羞愧的东西
What is something for which you feel shame?
羞愧
Shame.
我小时候 我的狗狗死了 那是我的错
My dog died when I was a kid. It was my fault.
为什么
Why?
我忘了关门
I left the gate open.
你在哪儿出生
Where were you born?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
现在是几月
What month is it?
你是说哪个季度
You mean, what quarter?
等等
Wait.
你的第一个记忆是什么
What is your first memory?
- 我不知道 - 告诉我
- I don't know. - Tell me.
天啊
Holy shit.
- 不知道 我不记得了 - 告诉我
- I don't know. I don't remember. - Tell me.
- 告诉我你的第一个记忆 - 我不记得了
- Tell me your first memory. - I don't remember.
嘿 桌上的
Hey there, you on the table.
不知道你愿不愿意做一个简短的问卷调查
I wonder if you'd mind taking a brief survey.
五个问题
Five questions.
首先 你是谁
To start out, who are you?